Guide to the Park Slope Civic Council (PSCC) records BCMS.0083
Brooklyn Collection
- Series 2: Carl Kaiserman papers, 1970-2004
  - Sub-series 2.5: Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS), 1970-2001
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Series 3: Mort Fleischer papers, 1977-2004
  Mort Fleischer was President of the Park Slope Civic Council from 1982 to 1984, and a Trustee after that until 2010. Fleischer was involved in Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS) and worked with Carl Kaiserman on efforts to recognize the area south of Park Slope. These efforts included a 1980 House Tour that focused on South Slope. Mort Fleischer received the George Lovgren Volunteer Award in 2011.
  Series 3: Mort Fleischer papers, 1977-2004, includes materials from Fleischer's involvement with the Park Slope Civic Council as President and Trustee. These materials include trustee meeting agendas and minutes, applications and reviews from the grants committee, House Tour finance files, and some files on subjects related to Park Slope. Most of the materials are from the years Fleischer was a Trustee.
  - Trustees Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Meetinngs, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - [Trustee meeting minutes], 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - [Trustee meeting minutes and agendas], 2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Park Slope Library [photographs], circa 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Grants Fall/Spring, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - [Veterans Committee Military Museum flyer], circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1995-2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Fifth Avenue Committee, 1977-1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - [Trustee and officer ballot, questionnaires, and directories], 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Housing, circa 1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Grants, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Grants, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Grants, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - [Grants], 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - [Grants], 1993 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - [Grants], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - [Grants], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Grant Applications, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Grant Applications, Spring and Fall, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - [House Tour contributions], 1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - [House Tour finances], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - [Budget Report by Quarter], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sponsors House Tour, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - [Park Slope and ROSAS maps], circa 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - [Trustee meeting materials], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Series 4: Park Slope Civic Council Administration, 1938-2009; 1960-2005
  Series 3: Park Slope Civic Council Administration, 1938-2009, includes meeting minutes and agendas, membership lists, flyers, mailers, community grant announcements, posters, and other office files related to the activities of the Park Slope Civic Council (some from when it was the South Brooklyn Board of Trade).
  Materials from the House Tour and Trustee meetings are well-represented in this series.
  The series is arranged into six sub-series:
  Sub-series 4.1: Meeting Materials, 1938-2005
  Sub-series 4.2: Community Grants Materials, 1981-2000
  Sub-series 4.3: Projects and Committees, 1965-2009
  Sub-series 4.4: Membership Materials, 1983-1993
  Sub-series 4.5: Civic News Production, 1964-2005
  Sub-series 4.6: House Tour Materials, 1961-2005
  - Sub-series 4.1: Meeting Materials, 1938-2005
    The sub-series is in chronological order.
    Sub-series 4.1: Meeting Materials, 1938-2005, includes meeting minutes, agendas, notes, and other materials used at Park Slope Civic Council meetings. Materials from Executive Board Meetings, Trustee Meetings, and Annual Meetings are represented in this sub-series. Many of the files have unknown creators, but notes and materials from Nancy McGregor, PSCC Secretary in the 1970s, and Vincent Lee, PSCC Secretary in the 1990s, are identified in the folder title.
    There are a few materials in this sub-series that relate to the Council when it was the South Brooklyn Board of Trade.
    - [South Brooklyn Board of Trade], 1938-1948 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - [Treasurers' files], 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - [Nancy McGregor, Secretary materials], 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - [Nancy McGregor, Secretary materials], 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - PSCC Trustees, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Park Slope [Trustee business materials], 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - [Constitution and by-laws], circa 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Park Slope [Trustee Meeting minutes], 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Park Slope [Trustee Meeting minutes], 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - [Trustee Meeting agendas and minutes], 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - [Trustee Meeting agendas and minutes], 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - [Trustee Meeting minutes], 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - [Trustee Meeting minutes], 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - [Trustee Meeting agendas and minutes], 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - [Executive and Trustee Meeting materials], 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - [Trustee Meeting agendas and minutes], 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - [Trustee Meeting agendas and minutes], 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 5, Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, Financial, etc., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council Board Members and Trustees], 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, etc. [from Trustee and Secretary Vincent Lee], 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, etc. [from Trustee and Secretary Vincent Lee], 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - [Executive Board Meeting and Trustee Meeting minutes], 1998-2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - [Trustee Meeting minutes and agendas], 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - [Executive Board Meeting and Trustee Meeting minutes], 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council Annual Meeting program], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council Annual Meeting programs], 2005 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 4.2: Community Grants Materials, 1981-2000
    The sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    Sub-series 4.2 Community Grants Materials, 1981-2000, includes grant applications, grant review notes, grant announcements, and other materials generated by the Park Slope Civic Council grants committee.
    - Grants, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Grants, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Grants, 1992-2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Grants [Letters to a Forest], 1995 (Box 13, Folder 18, Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 4.3: Projects and Committees, 1965-2009
    Sub-series 4.3: Projects and Committees, 1965-2005, includes correspondence, meeting minutes, news clippings, and flyers and other ephemera related to special projects and committees of the Park Slope Civic Council.
    - [Eighth Street Neighbors], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - [Park Slope elected officials], 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - [Eighth Street Neighbors], circa 2003 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council committees], circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - [Neighborhoods Council for Downtown Brooklyn Landmarks meeting agenda], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - General finance, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council news briefs], 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - [Scholarship Committee], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - [United States Postal Service, application to mail at the special bulk rate], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - [IRS letter 501(c)(3)], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - [Old First Reformed Church and Park Slope Civic Council], circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - [Community Safety Forum flyer], circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - [Toys for Tots Drive flyer], circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - [The Park Slope Paper, February 12, 2005] (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - [Project Reach Youth oral history project], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - [Projects and proposals], 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - [Resignation letters], 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - [Complaints and requests for review], 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - [Fall 2004 Clean Streets event proposal] (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Clippings, printed material collected by Dr. Howard Hanning, 1966-1977 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 9th Street history from Bill Novak, Dr. Howard Hanning, circa 1997 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Byrne Park ad Prospect Park - Rosalie Friend's file, 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Park Slope history 6th Street Prospect Park West Block Association, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - PSCC - Trustees - Individuals, Sawyer, Tom Award, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - PSCC - Trustees - Individuals, Lovgren, George, Death, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - PSCC Exhibit at the Brooklyn Museum, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - [Park Slope-related news clippings], 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - [Prospect Park YMCA Seamen's House premiere], 2002 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - [Brooklyn Center for the Urban Environment (BCUE)], 2002 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - [Gallery 55 show opening flyers], circa 1965 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - [Community Volunteer Fair flyer], 2005 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - ["The Conservation of Park Slope" profile], circa 1966 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - [Lipsitz and Union Development Group], 1999 (Box 13, Folder 51, Box 22, Folder 10)
    - [Commerce Bank drive-thru petition], circa 2005 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - [Carroll Gardens Association 20th Anniversary news clipping], 1991 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - [East New York Savings Bank donation], 1991 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - [Historic district meeting planning], 2001-2005 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - [Fort Greene Park urban forest management plan], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - [Wall Street Journal "The Lager Challenge" article], 2005 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - [Brooklyn Technical High School 9/11 plaque draft], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - [Friends of the Park Slope Branch Library], 1998 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - [100th anniversary speech], circa 1996 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - [Community Consulting Services Traffic-Transit Challenge], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - [Stop the Expansion, Poly Prep Lower School], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Sub-series 4.4: Membership Materials, 1983-1993
    Sub-series 4.4: Membership Materials, 1983-1993, includes lists of members, records of membership renewals, and information from their yearly membership drive.
    - Membership Drive Info, 1983-1992 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Membership, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Membership Monthly Renewal Lists, 1984-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Membership Monthly Renewal Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Membership Monthly Renewal Lists, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 4.5: Civic News Production, 1964-2005
    Sub-series 4.5: Civic News Production, 1964-2005, includes notes with ideas for Civic News issues, news clippings, and documentation with standards for printing and publication.
    - [1966 Civic News articles gathered by Tom Sawyer], 1966-1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - [1966 Civic News articles gathered by Tom Sawyer], 1966-1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Civic News - General, 1985-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 50th anniversary Civic News, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - [Brooklyn Historical Society Civic News binding], 1991-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - ["Spanish Vaults in Brooklyn" 1966 article], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Civic News - December, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - CN [Civic News] tech standards, circa 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Civic News ideas, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Civic News - July, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - [Civic News publication], 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 4.6: House Tour Materials, 1961-2005
    The annual Park Slope House Tour started in 1959 as a way to attract home owners to the neighborhood. Private homes and landmarks are opened to the public and ticket sales benefit the Park Slope Civic Council. Other neighborhood organizations in Brooklyn sponsor similar house tours, such as the Brooklyn Heights Association and the Prospect Lefferts Gardens Neighbordhood Association (PLGNA).
    Sub-series 4.6: House Tour Materials, 1961-2005, includes correspondence, posters, mailers, schedules, and financial records related to the Park Slope Civic Council House Tour.
    - House Tour materials given by Bill Novak, circa 1961-1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - [House Tour materials], 1961 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - [House Tour materials], 1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - [House Tour materials], 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - [House Tour materials], 1966 (Box 19, Folder 4, Box 23, Folder 11)
    - [House Tour materials], 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5, Box 23)
    - [House Tour materials], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6, Box 23)
    - [House Tour materials], 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7, Box 23, Folder 12)
    - [House Tour materials], 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Houses used 1971-1991, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - [House Tour materials], 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - House Tour posters, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - [House Tour materials], 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - [House Tour materials], 1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 1978 House Tour contributions (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - [House Tour materials], 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - [House Tour materials], 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - [House Tour materials], 1978-1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 1979 House Tour Bank Contributions (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - [House Tour materials], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - 1980 House Tour Bank Contributions (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - House Tour, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - [House Tour materials], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - House Tour Contributions Financial Institutions, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - [House Tour materials], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - [House Tour contribution thank you letters], 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - House Tour, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - House Tour Contributions Financial Institutions, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - House Tour Contributions Financial Institutions, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - House Tour, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - [House Tour materials], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - [House Tour materials], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - [House Tour materials], 1983 (Box 14, Folder 31, Box 24, Folder 7)
    - [House Tour materials], 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - [House Tour materials], 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - [House Tour materials], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - [House Tour materials], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - [House Tour materials], 1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - [House Tour materials], 1986 (Box 14, Folder 34, Box 24, Folder 8)
    - [House Tour materials], 1987 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - House Tour, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 35, Box 24, Folder 9)
    - [House Tour materials], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - [House Tour materials], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - [House Tour materials], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 37, Box 22, Folder 7)
    - [House Tour materials], 1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - [House Tour promotional photographs], circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - [House Tour planning materials], 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 39, Box 22, Folder 9)
    - [House Tour materials], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - House Tour, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - [House Tour materials], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - House Tour, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 43, Box 24, Folder 4)
    - House Tour, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 44, Box 22, Box 8)
    - House Tour schedule/plan, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - House Tour, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - [House Tour materials], 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - [House Tour materials], 1996 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Letters/House-sitters, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - [House Tour materials], 1996 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - House Tour, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      Includes three 3.5 inch floppy disks that have not been imaged. The floppy disks are not available for research.
    - [House Tour] Correspondence, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - [House Tour press], 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - House Tour Correspondence, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - House Tour, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Landmark Campaign Research, circa 1960
  Series 5: Landmark Campaign Research, circa 1960, includes typewritten research and handwritten notes with ownership, directory, and architectural information of lots in Park Slope. The research covers tax blocks 939 to 1073.
  The series is in original order, which is in numeric order by block numbers.
  Biographical / Historical
  The Landmark Campaign was the Park Slope Civic Council's project to achieve historic district designation from the NYC Landmarks Preservation Commission (LPC) for 1,800 buildings in Park Slope in 1973. This initial designation from the LPC covered the area of Park Slope closest to Prospect Park.
  - NB I [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - NB I [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - NB II [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - NB II [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - NB Research III [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - NB Research IV [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - NB Research V [New Building], circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Series 6: Civic News Issues, 1938-2018
  This series is in chronological order.
  Series 6: Civic News Issues, 1938-2018, includes unbound issues of the Park Slope Civic Council's newsletter Civic News.
  The first issue of Civic News was published in April 1938 under the South Brooklyn Board of Trade. It features reports and updates from Council committees and the Board of Trustees, and articles solicited from members of the community.
  - Civic News, South Brooklyn Board of Trade, Vols. 1-3, 1938-1940 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Civic News, South Brooklyn Board of Trade, Vols. 4-16, 1941-1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Civic News, South Brooklyn Board of Trade, Vols. 4-16, 1948-1953 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 23-26, 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 23-26, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 27-29, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 27-29, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 27-29, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 30-33, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 30-33, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 30-33, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 30-33, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 34-36, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 34-36, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 34-36, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 37-39, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 37-39, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 37-39, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 40-45, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 46-49, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 46-49, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 46-49, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 46-49, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 50-, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 50-, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 50-, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 50-, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Civic News, Park Slope Civic Council, Vols. 50-, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - [Civic News issues], 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - [Civic News issues], 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - [Civic News issues], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - [Civic News issues], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - [Civic News issues], 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - [Civic News issues], 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - [Civic News issues], 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - [Civic News issues], 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - [Civic News issues], 2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - [Civic News issues], 2001 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - [Civic News issues], 2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - [Civic News issues], 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - [Civic News issues], 2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - [Civic News issues], 2005 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - [Civic News issues], 2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - [Civic News issues], 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - [Civic News issues], 2008 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - [Civic News issues], 2009 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - [Civic News issues], 2010 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - [Civic News issues], 2011 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - [Civic News issues], 2012 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - [Civic News issues], 2013-2017 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - [Civic News issues], 2018 (Box 21, Folder 7)